<users>
  <user>
    <username>MarkGeralt</username>
    <reviews>
      <review>
        <gameTitle>Ghost of Tsushima</gameTitle>
        <commentary>Amazing to see what Sucker Punch has achieved going from Infamous Series to Ghost of Tsushima. The game looks gorgeous. My biggest take is the absence of HUD, so you get to immerse yourself in the environment as the wind is used to guide you to your next location. My biggest gripe with most open-world games is having to spend half the time looking at the mini-map and this game solves it beautifully. Also, there is no level gating, where you can&apos;t fight an enemy because they are 30 levels above you. The combat is fluid and really satisfying (playing on hard). The loading times in the game are only a few seconds, which is surprising given it is running on HDD and such old hardware. The photo mode is rich with features. The customization and charms are fun. I feel this is the game that everyone wanted an Assassin&apos;s Creed in Japan to be. Overall, I have really enjoyed the hours I have put into this game. Congrats to Sucker Punch on this great game.</commentary>
        <date>Jul 18, 2020</date>
        <score>10</score>
      </review>
      <review>
        <gameTitle>The Last of Us Part II</gameTitle>
        <commentary>Great Gameplay - Gorgeous Landscape - Terrible Story The first Last of Us is still one of my favorites, so this game was a 7 year long wait. Technically, the game is no different than other Naughty Dog games. Every gameplay mechanic is improved and built upon. I found stealth to be more enjoyable. Every encounter is different. It is a semi-open linear world, so there are multiple paths you can take where you might or might not encounter certain enemies. NPC (unlike previous games) have names and react when one of their fellow mates get killed. The game is gruesome and violent but that is to be expected given the current state of the world in the Last of Us. It&apos;s also amazing what Naughty dog has achieved graphically on a PS4 Pro where the game is running on 1440p@30fps. Unfortunately, on the other hand, the story has left me with a lot to desire. The first few hours feel rushed and questionable, however, I thought this would lead to an ending not possible without taking this direction. However, the ending has to be one of the worst game endings of a AAA game in recent memory. Character-wise it makes no sense. I don&apos;t want to post any spoilers so I will say this. &quot;It can&apos;t all be for nothing&quot; would describe part I. &quot;It was all for nothing&quot; would describe part II.</commentary>
        <date>Jun 19, 2020</date>
        <score>5</score>
      </review>
    </reviews>
  </user>
  <user>
    <username>Alajme</username>
    <reviews>
      <review>
        <gameTitle>Ghost of Tsushima</gameTitle>
        <commentary>Very ambitious game from Sucker punch the developers of Infamous and sly games , Ghost of Tsushima takes off slow through the story but it gets interesting and better each time as you continue the story , the world is so beautiful filled with a lot of activities to enjoy , the wind system really makes the game special and refreshing , there’s no need to open the map every time , highly recommend the game</commentary>
        <date>Jul 18, 2020</date>
        <score>10</score>
      </review>
      <review>
        <gameTitle>Final Fantasy VII Remake</gameTitle>
        <commentary>I have just completed the FF7R , and all I have to say is just WOW , it’s incredible faithful Remake with some twists to the story that ended up being Great</commentary>
        <date>May 8, 2020</date>
        <score>9</score>
      </review>
    </reviews>
  </user>
</users>